<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-05-16T23:01:49+02:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Jordi’s blog</title><subtitle>My personal website.</subtitle><author><name>Jordi Puig Rabat</name><email>jordipuig37@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">Welcome To My Website</title><link href="/welcome-to-my-website/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome To My Website" /><published>2021-05-15T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2021-05-15T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/welcome-to-my-website</id><content type="html" xml:base="/welcome-to-my-website/">&lt;body&gt;
    &lt;p align=&quot;justify&quot;&gt;
        This is the first post in my website, so this is meant to be both a test –I'm testing how does this works– and an introduction for the reader. This webpage is a personal and professional profile, here I will post things I do related to Data Science, professional information like my portfolio, my CV and, why not, posts in a less formal style to express opinions or whatnot.
        &lt;br&gt;
        For those who don't know me I would like to present myself. I'm a &lt;a href=&quot;https://dse.upc.edu/en&quot;&gt;Data Science and Engineering&lt;/a&gt; student at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.upc.edu/en?set_language=en&quot;&gt;UPC&lt;/a&gt;, in Barcelona. I'm interested in Artificial Intelligence, Data Analysis and Data Science in general. I also like the more computational part of what I'm studying, like algorithmics and programming per se. I use python most of the time but I also know R, C++, SQL, &lt;del&gt;unfortunately&lt;/del&gt; Matlab, learning HTML. I think when you have a general idea of what programming is, learning a new language is similar to learning a new python library.
        &lt;br&gt;
        Aside from my interests related to my sudy field, I also want to add other things I enjoy to make it more personal. I always loved playing music, I play the saxophone and the guitar. I'm not a good singer but sometimes I play guitar and sing with friends. I also enjoy camping and hicking, either by the sea or by the mountain, what I like the most of this is the contact with nature.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;
        I hope this worked as a personal and website presentation. If you need to contact me, feel free to mail me or contact me through Linkedin ;).
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;</content><author><name>Jordi Puig Rabat</name><email>jordipuig37@gmail.com</email></author><summary type="html">This is the first post in my website, so this is meant to be both a test –I'm testing how does this works– and an introduction for the reader. This webpage is a personal and professional profile, here I will post things I do related to Data Science, professional information like my portfolio, my CV and, why not, posts in a less formal style to express opinions or whatnot. For those who don't know me I would like to present myself. I'm a Data Science and Engineering student at UPC, in Barcelona. I'm interested in Artificial Intelligence, Data Analysis and Data Science in general. I also like the more computational part of what I'm studying, like algorithmics and programming per se. I use python most of the time but I also know R, C++, SQL, unfortunately Matlab, learning HTML. I think when you have a general idea of what programming is, learning a new language is similar to learning a new python library. Aside from my interests related to my sudy field, I also want to add other things I enjoy to make it more personal. I always loved playing music, I play the saxophone and the guitar. I'm not a good singer but sometimes I play guitar and sing with friends. I also enjoy camping and hicking, either by the sea or by the mountain, what I like the most of this is the contact with nature. I hope this worked as a personal and website presentation. If you need to contact me, feel free to mail me or contact me through Linkedin ;).</summary></entry></feed>